lollywollydoodle.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy – Lolly Wolly Doodle

Effective January 9, 2012

LOLLY WOLLY DOODLE

PRIVACY POLICY

Welcome to Lolly Wolly Doodle! Your privacy, and the privacy of all registered users of lollwollydoodle.com, is important to us. Accordingly, we have adopted the following privacy policy. Our policy is based on the principles of notice, choice, access and security in the collection and use of all information regarding our users and their activities at our site.

1. Applicability

This privacy policy applies to your usage of the lollywollydoodle.com website and to any information that we collect from you from our partner sites, including but not limited to our page on Facebook (collectively, the "Sites").

2. Notice

This policy tells you, among other things, what information we gather from you, how we may use or disclose that information and our efforts to protect it. Please read this policy carefully, and feel free to contact us at [privacy@lollywollydoodle.com](mailto:privacy@lollywollydoodle.com) if you have any questions regarding its contents.

Types of Information Collected

In connection with your use of our Sites, we ask for and may collect a variety of information from and about you in different ways. For example, when you register to use any of our Sites, we ask for and store your and/or your business' name, address, email address and other identifying contact data. In addition, we collect photos that you share with us (including but not limited to photos posted on our Facebook wall), information that you supply regarding purchases (including but not limited to the monogram or size information), information that you supply in response to a promotion, game or sweepstakes (on Facebook or otherwise), the clicks you make on our website or on Facebook, any information you supply in response to a survey (whether on Facebook, via email or on our website), the fact that you responded to a particular promotion, information that you supply about your contacts, technical information (including but not limited to your computer and browser type and IP address) and testimonials about a product or our company. We may also collect the information you disclose in any of our chat rooms, discussion groups and bulletin boards.

Use of Cookies

Use of our Sites requires that you accept the use of cookies, which are small data files that our website (and those of our partners) sends to your browser for storage on your computer's hard drive. We may use cookies to protect confidential data, track activity at our Sites and better serve your needs and interests.

Use of Information

We use your personally identifying information to identify and register you as a user of a Site, change the amounts of virtual currencies or points that you have, promote our products and services, personalize our products and services including but not limited to the offers that we provide to you (including but not limited to personalizing our products and services based on any information that you authorize Facebook or another Site to provide to us), target advertizing based on certain profiles of interests that you have (including but not limited to information that you authorize Facebook or another Site to provide to us), target your friends or connections on Facebook or another Site, suggest that you recommend that a friend make a purchase of a product from us, create slideshows or other photo montages based on your submissions and to protect our interests, including but not limited to enforcing the Terms of Service or to protect against fraud or misuse. We may use your email address or message you via Facebook or another service to contact you directly regarding services or products that we believe may be of interest to you (which may include the products of our trusted partners). We may also associate your personally identifying information with information we collect about your preferences and activities at a Site, such as the particular pages you request at a Site and purchases or other transactions you effect through a Site, and with information that we collect through sources other than our Sites. We may vary the content you receive in future visits to a Site based on your preferences and activities.

We may combine your personally identifying information, and information about your preferences and activities, with those of all or a particular group of our users to prepare collective profiles of our users and their activities. For example, we may track the number of our users who view certain pages or use certain features or compile the total dollar amount of sales conducted through our site in a particular geographic region. Such information, and other information we derive from individual users' information, allows us to continue to grow and provide you with quality fellow users through more accurate marketing and advertising of our website.

Disclosure of Information

We may provide your personally identifying information, and information about your activities and preferences, to other companies wishing to contact you about products or services, but only to those that we believe impose reasonable safeguards on the privacy of your information. We may also provide these companies with collective profiles of our user groups and their activities and preferences. Such collective profiles may also be disclosed in describing our site and services to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes.

We may work with third party advertising services providers who may use their own cookies to measure how many times advertising content has been viewed and to serve you advertising that may be more relevant to you. For more information on such practices and an opportunity to opt-out of them, please visit http://www.aboutads.info.

In the event that a third party merges with us, acquires us or acquires our assets related to the information that you have provided, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information that we have collected from you as part of that merger, acquisition or acquisition of assets.

Finally, we may disclose information to fulfill certain legal and regulatory requirements or if we believe, in good faith, that such disclosure is legally required or necessary to protect others' rights or to prevent harm.

International Users

If you are visiting a Site from the European Union or another country or territory outside of the United States ("U.S."), please note that any data you provide will be transferred outside the European Union or such other non-U.S. territory for use by us for any of the purposes described herein. By providing any data to us, you hereby consent to such transfers of your data to the U.S.

3. Choice

You may choose to restrict our use of your information to maintaining your account on the Site, or prohibit our disclosure of your information to others, by contacting us and directing us to impose such limits. For example, if requested, we will not provide your information to any third parties, regardless of the steps they may take to protect such information. If you do not wish us to provide your information to third parties, or otherwise wish us to restrict the use or disclosure of your information, please send us an e-mail at [privacy@lollywollydoodle.com](mailto:privacy@lollywollydoodle.com).

In addition, we will not send unsolicited messages to users of our site who indicate that they do not wish to receive such messages. If you do not wish to receive unsolicited email or Facebook messages from us, please contact us at [privacy@lollywollydoodle.com](mailto:privacy@lollywollydoodle.com).

4. Access

At any time after you have logged on to our site, you may contact us at [privacy@lollywollydoodle.com](mailto:privacy@lollywollydoodle.com) to request access to information we have collected regarding you or your business or to notify us of changes to such information. If you request any such changes, we will contact you by email or fax to confirm those changes. Once confirmed, any new item of information will replace the corresponding information previously provided.

5. Security

We use industry-standard encryption methods to transmit your personal registration information from your computer to ours across the Internet, and we restrict access to any transactional portions of our site to computers running web browsers that support Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") protocol. To use this protection technology, you need to have an SSL-capable browser, such as Netscape Navigator 4.5 or higher, Microsoft Internet Explorer 4.5 or higher, Mozilla Firefox 2.0 or higher or Google Chrome 1.0 or higher. These browsers will automatically activate the technology when you log on to our site.

Please remember that you play a valuable part in security as well. Your password to access our site, which you select at registration, should never be shared with anyone and should be changed frequently. After you have finished using our site, you should log off and exit your browser so no unauthorized persons can use our site with your name and account information. Remember that any information you voluntarily disclose online in any news or message postings, discussion groups or chat rooms may be collected and used by others without your permission. Furthermore, if you provide any information to parties who operate websites that are linked to or from our Site or a Site governed by this policy, different rules may apply to their collection, use or disclosure of your personal information. We encourage you to review these sites' policies before revealing any sensitive or personal information.

Regardless of the precautions taken by you or by us, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you transmit such information at your own risk. E-mail communications, in particular, are not secure.

Special Policy on Information Regarding Teens (persons 13 to 17 years of age)

Teens are required to provide the email address of a parent or guardian before submitting any personally identifiable information. A notification message is sent to the parent or guardian of all guests who identify themselves as being between 13 and 17 years of age, which discloses the information provided by the teen and allows the parent or guardian to be aware of and participate in the teen's online experience.

Changes to Privacy Policy.

From time to time, we may modify this policy to reflect changes in the way we collect and use information or changes in privacy-related laws, regulations and industry standards. Accordingly, we reserve the right to change this policy at any time by posting the revised policy on this website. Data will be handled in accordance with the policy in effect at the time the data is used, subject to the user's right to opt out of revisions to this policy implemented since the data was first collected.
